<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on Dakota Nelson</title>
    <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on Dakota Nelson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dakotanelson.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/art/</guid>
      <description>Artists I Like In which I keep a running log of people whose art I enjoy.
Hopefully you didn&amp;rsquo;t think this was going to be about art I had made.
Waneella Site: https://waneella.tumblr.com/
Some of my favorite art is pixel art.
Atelier Olschinsky Site: https://artstore.olschinsky.at/de/artists/atelier-olschinsky-0.php
Greg Stones Site: https://the-zombie-penguin.myshopify.com/
Trevor Paglen Site: http://www.paglen.com
Really great works on surveillance and technology. I especially love &amp;ldquo;They Watch the Moon.&amp;rdquo;
James Gilleard Site: http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/books/</guid>
      <description>Books! I love them dearly.
But First&amp;hellip; Before we start, I would like to take this time to encourage you to try out Libby: https://meet.libbyapp.com/.
It&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic app you can use to check out library eBooks. Seriously life-changing.
Ok, now into the books. This isn&amp;rsquo;t a complete list, for an assortment of reasons, the primary one being that I don&amp;rsquo;t always keep track of everything I read, especially ones I consider to be more like textbooks (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/contact/</guid>
      <description>I am a hermit. Nonetheless, you may find me in the following places.
https://keybase.io/dakota
https://www.linkedin.com/in/dakotanelson/
https://github.com/dakotanelson/
dakota (big ol dot, &amp;ldquo;.&amp;quot;, you know the one) w (., again) nelson at the google mail place where email goes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/coursera/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/coursera/</guid>
      <description>Coursera I spend a lot of time studying things I find interesting; it&amp;rsquo;s an odd hobby but there you have it. Coursera plays a fairly large part in that.
My profile is here: https://www.coursera.org/user/c0937fc573eefc8c9d2272de12406533
I did the original two Udacity courses waaaay back when, but my account appears not to work any longer (I assume they moved fast and broke things) and I haven&amp;rsquo;t bothered to email them.
For some reason, I never got much into edX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/experience/</guid>
      <description>Work Security Consultant, Leviathan Security Group April 2020 - Present
Pentester and Security Researcher, Black Hills Information Security February 2017 - April 2020
Consulting, research, development, and a whole lot more.
Principal Consultant, Striker Security May 2016 - January 2018
I ran a small information security consulting company. The company is still around, but I don&amp;rsquo;t do all that much with it anymore.
Software Development Intern, Nylas January 2016 - May 2016</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/interests/</guid>
      <description>Interests I have&amp;hellip; way too many, and pursue them with varying degrees of time investment and zeal. Here are a few.
Information Security Wilderness Medicine Robots Space SPAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACE
Forecasting/Foresight/Future Studies Finance &amp;amp; Monetary Policy National Security/Arms Control/Intelligence/OSINT Strategy/History Synthetic Biology Risk Management Disaster Preparedness, Recovery, and Response Learning/Human Cognitive Performance This was kicked off by &amp;ldquo;Learning how to Learn&amp;rdquo; on Coursera and I&amp;rsquo;ve since read PILES of books about it. Things like spaced repetition (in the form of Anki) have shown strong enough results for me that I&amp;rsquo;m now hooked and want more understanding of how to make my brain better at doing what I want it to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/media/</guid>
      <description>Talks/Webcasts Tweets, Beats, and Sheets: C2 Over Social Media In which I discuss how to control malware using Twitter, Soundcloud, Google Sheets, and Salesforce.
Link: https://www.blackhillsinfosec.com/webcast-tweets-beats-and-sheets-c2-over-social-media/
Social Media C2 The original talk about the sneaky-creeper social media C2 library at BSides Las Vegas.
Link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tLkQH-ev2iw
There&amp;rsquo;s a companion blog post here if you want more detail.
Monitoring Social Media in 5 Minutes a Week Introducing my pushpin-web project, which collects and displays geotagged social media in areas the user specifies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/me/programming/</guid>
      <description>Programming You can find me on GitHub, which is likely to be the best way to see exactly what I&amp;rsquo;m working on at any given time.
A fair bit of the code I work on isn&amp;rsquo;t public, but ipso facto that means I can&amp;rsquo;t talk about it anyway.
Generally, my projects have one or more of these characteristics:
 offensive security (i.e. malware) data aggregation/analysis OSINT  Favorite and/or Noteworthy Projects Sneaky-creeper tl;dr command and control for malware over social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/this-site/inspiration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/docs/this-site/inspiration/</guid>
      <description>Inspiration This site was inspired by a great many things - but most especially by several other websites I enjoy out on the internet.
https://rogerstrunk.com/
https://www.gwern.net/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>