<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Dakota Nelson</title>
    <link>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Dakota Nelson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dakotanelson.com/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tweets, Beats, and Sheets: C2 Over Social Media</title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/tweets-beats-sheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/tweets-beats-sheets/</guid>
      <description>This webcast explains and demonstrates using sneaky-creeper to control a simple implant over several different third-part sites.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media C2</title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/social-media-c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/social-media-c2/</guid>
      <description>This talk at BSides Las Vegas 2015 covers Sneaky-creeper, a python library that allows for command and control over third-party sites such as Twitter, Tumblr, SalesForce, Google Sheets, and SoundCloud. The library is designed for ease of use, and has an API much like that of a standard &amp;ldquo;internet socket&amp;rdquo;-type library (except, of course, that the bits are flowing over third-party services).
  
There is a companion blog post to this talk here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security of the Near Field Communication Protocol</title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/nfc-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/nfc-security/</guid>
      <description>This paper, published my senior year of high school in the Journal of Computing Sciences in Colleges, gives an overview of near field communication (NFC) security.
The abstract is:
 With the booming of smartphone and wireless networks, contactless payment systems have been gradually accepted by a range of sectors and industries. Near Field Communication (NFC), as a de facto standard for radio communication, dominates this market and has accumulated many applications, such as use as a digital wallet and ticketing system, due to its convenience and versatility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Social Media in 5 Minutes a Week</title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/monitoring-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/monitoring-social-media/</guid>
      <description>This talk at SOURCE Boston covers the design and use of pushpin-web, a python project which allows for collection of geotagged social media data from several different platforms in near real-time.
  
There is a companion project page for this talk here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Recoll</title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/total-recoll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/total-recoll/</guid>
      <description>This talk at the DEF CON 25 Recon Village covers Recoll, a full-text search tool which I&amp;rsquo;ve found to be incredibly useful.
  
There is a companion blog post to this talk here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steganography: The Art and Science of Hiding Things in Other Things</title>
      <link>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/steganography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dakotanelson.com/publications/steganography/</guid>
      <description>This series of blog posts introduces the reader to steganography, the practice of concealing a file, message, image, or video within another file, message, image, or video. It then builds on that foundation to introduce error correcting codes - specifically, Hamming codes - and some of the math behind it all.
The sample code which formed the nucleus for this series was part of a class project for my discrete math class in college, and can be found on Github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>